Pablo Adrián Uboldi

Software Engineer | Aerospace Engineer

I am a professional software developer with experience working in Python, Django, Flask, HTML, CSS/Bootstrap and Javascript. I am a fast learner and a self-taught person - my previous job experiences have driven me to learn diverse specialized software, such as Mathematica, SolidWorks, AutoCAD, Simscale or Matlab. I also hold a degree in Aerospace Engineering, class of 2021, from the National Technology University in Buenos Aires.



pablouboldi89@gmail.com

Ciudad de México, México

github.com/pablouboldi

5585733783

pablouboldi-website.herokuapp.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Software Engineer Freelance

07/2022 - Present

CDMX. México

- Integration of social and cryptocurrency profiles for analysis.
- Development of a Discord Bot to collect user data.
- Web UX development for impact measurement in digital marketing campaigns, for a startup.
- Development of a Python script for solving Taylor-Maccoll equations for supersonic flow around a cone. For university use.

Fluid Mechanics Associate Professor National Technology University

03/2018 - Present

Buenos Aires, Argentina

- I oversee the theoretical and practical evaluation activities developed for the students of Aerospace Engineering.
- Class dictation.

Project Manager

Natural and Exact Sciences Faculty, UBA

03/2014 - 08/2021

Buenos Aires, Argentina

- I was part of the Technical Department, co-leading the electrical maintenance team for small and medium scale projects.
- I collaborated with the IT Department in software support and troubleshooting of staff's PCs.

Formula SAE Aerodynamics team Co-Director

National Technology University

11/2019 - 06/2020

Buenos Aires, Argentina

 I was part of the decision-making process regarding the design of the competition car.

SKILLS

Python

Diango

Flask

CSS/Bootstrap

HTML

AutoCAD

SolidWorks

Mathematic

Office Suite

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Personal Website (06/2022 - 06/2022)

• https://pablouboldi-website.herokuapp.com

To-do List Website (05/2022 - 05/2022)

https://pablo-todo-list.herokuapp.com

Breakout Game (04/2022 - 04/2022)

• https://github.com/pablouboldi/breakout-game

EDUCATION

Aerospace Engineer National Technology University

rtacionat recimotogy om

03/2008 - 05/2021

Buenos Aires, Argentina

Electronic and Electromechanics TechnicianPhilips Argentina Technology Institute

03/2002 - 11/2007

Buenos Aires, Argentina

LANGUAGES

Spanish

English

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

Football

Paddle

Videogames

PC Masterrace